amitree.com 2017-01-02

# Amitree - Privacy Policy

## Your Privacy Rights

This policy is effective as of and was last updated on 4/15/2016 

### Welcome

Thanks for using **Amitree**. This is our Privacy Policy. 

While the law requires us to post this policy, we take your privacy very seriously and, as such, we think it is important to describe how we collect, use and protect your information when you access our website(s), products, services and applications (collectively, the “Services”). 

### What does this Privacy Policy cover?

This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) that we gather when you are accessing or using our Services, but not to the practices of companies we don’t own or control, or people that we don’t manage. We gather various types of Personal Information from our users, as explained in more detail below, and we use this Personal Information internally in connection with our Services, including to personalize, provide, and improve our services, to allow you to set up a user account and profile, to contact you in connection to your use of our Services, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to analyze how you use the Services. In certain cases, we may also share some Personal Information with third parties, but only as described below. 

###  Children Under 13 

It’s kind of obvious, since children can’t buy or sell a house, but the Services are not intended for children under 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, we have no idea why you would be trying to use our Services, but please do not attempt to register for the Services or send any personal information about yourself to us. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that a child under 13 may have provided us personal information, please contact us at [privacy@amitree.com](mailto:privacy@amitree.%63om). 

###  Privacy Policy Changes 

Each time you use the Service, the current version of this Privacy Policy will apply. Each time you use the Service you should check the date of this Privacy Policy (which appears at the top of this document) and review any changes since the last time you used the site. We will alert you to changes by doing one or more of: a) placing a notice on the www.amitree.com, b) sending you an email, c) some other means. If you’ve opted not to receive emails from us, or if you haven’t provided us with your email address, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Services, and you are still responsible for reading and understanding them. If you use the Services after any changes to the Privacy Policy have been posted, it means you agree to all of the changes. 

###  Service Intended for United States and Canadian Residents 

The Service is hosted on servers in the United States of America and is intended for use for real estate transactions in the United States and Canada. 

###  What Information does Amitree Collect? 

###  Information You Provide to Us: 

To create a great experience for users of our Services, Amitree collects a range of Personal Information from and about Service users. We receive and store any information you or others on your home buying team provide to us. 

For example, some of the Personal Information collected is information provided by you when you sign up for the Services, or while interacting with us. That information may include your name, email address, mailing address, and detailed information about a home purchase, including address, financial details, details about the purchase contract, and other information related to the purchase of a residential home. We ask this information to deliver to you a more personally relevant experience. 

Other information may be provided by others on your home buying team. Members of the team may provide and share personal information about you or other team members, and about the home purchase. If you use the Service, you consent to the use and disclosure of Personal Information about you with anyone else who is using the Service and with whom you have shared the Personal information or who has Personal Information about you. This includes information about the home purchase and its financing. 

If you provide us with the name and email address of someone you want to be invited to open an account with us – a friend, real estate agent, lawyer, contractor or anyone else -- we only use that information to contact them about the Service. 

We may also use Personal Information you or your home buying team provides to us to help provide accurate insurance premium rate quotes; provide insurers with the required information for applications; communicate with you (or your clients, if you are a real estate professional) regarding insurance products; and bind insurance policies. 

If you authenticate your Google account (using Google / Gmail’s service), giving us permission to access your account, some content and/or information in those accounts (“Third Party Account Information”) may be transmitted into your account with us, and that Third Party Account Information transmitted to our Services is covered by this Privacy Policy. For example, Amitree may securely access or store your name, your Gmail email address, your Gmail emails and other conversations, and your Gmail contact list (including any images attached to contacts in the list). The content and/or information stored in those accounts is treated in the same way as the information described above. Certain information is required to register with us or to take advantage of some of our features. 

We may communicate with you by email, telephone, or text message if you’ve provided us the means to do so. For example, if you’ve given us your email address, we may send you emails describing our products and services, or email you about your use of the Services. Also, we may receive a confirmation when you open an email from us or click on a link in an email from us. This confirmation helps us make our communications with you more relevant to you and improve our Services. 

If you do not want to receive communications from us, please indicate as such in your account settings or inform us by sending an email to: [privacy@amitree.com](mailto:privacy@amitree.%63om). 

###  Information Collected Automatically 

Whenever you interact with our Services, we automatically receive and record information from your browser or device in our server logs, which may include your IP address, device identification, “cookie” information, the type of browser and/or device you’re using to access our Services, the page or feature you requested, or the information you submit as part of the request your browser and/or device makes to our servers. “Cookies” are identifiers we transfer to your browser or device that allow us to recognize your browser or device, keep you logged in to the Service, and tell us how and when pages and features in our Services are visited and by how many people. You may be able to change the preferences on your browser or device to prevent or limit your device’s acceptance of cookies, but this may prevent you from using the Service or taking advantage of some of our features. We may use this data to customize content for you that we think you might like, based on how you use our Services. We may also use it to improve the Services – for example, this data can tell us what types of problems users encounter when interacting with the Services, and we can use that knowledge to improve the Services and how they work for you and others. 

###  Information Collected by Other Websites and Do Not Track Policy 

Your browser may offer you a “Do Not Track” option, which allows you to signal to operators of websites and web applications and services (including behavioral advertising services) that you do not wish such operators to track certain of your online activities over time and across different websites. Our Services do not support Do Not Track requests at this time, which means that we may collect information about your online activity both while you are using the Services and after you leave our Services. This is our Do Not Track policy. We can’t and don’t make any promises about how third parties react when you set this signal on your browser. 

We provide links to websites that Amitree does not own or operate. Those sites too may collect Personal Information. We do not control or have access to that Personal Information, and the collection and use of your personal information by those other websites will be governed by the privacy policy applicable to that site. The privacy policies of other websites should identify the entity collecting your Personal Information, and how it is being used. Amitree is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non-Amitree websites, even if we link to them. Review the privacy policy of those sites before using them. 

###  Third Party Analytics Services 

We use third party analytics services to obtain, compile and analyze Information (that may include Personally Identifying Information) about how users are using and interacting with the Services. Some information is automatically collected from or about you when you use our Services. The analytics services may also collect the following from your use of our Services: the time of an event, how you came to Amitree’s site, what search engine and search keywords you may have used to get to our site, information about the device you are on such as your operating system, and browser, as well as your city/country location, tokens and IDs for push notifications. In addition, we may collect on our behalf data such as your age, IP addresses, user names, real names, email and email addresses, and other custom properties. We may provide Information (including Personally Identifying Information) to these analytics providers for the purpose of obtaining statistics and other information about how users are using and interacting with the Services. These analytics providers may use tracking techniques other than HTTP cookies to recognize your computer or device and/or to collect or compile this information. These techniques may be used directly on the Services. Amitree has no responsibility for the technologies, tools or practices of the third parties that providing analytics products and services to us. Your web browser may not permit you to block the use of these techniques, and that browser settings that block conventional cookies may have no effect on such techniques. 

###  Sharing of Your Personal Information by Amitree. 

We do not rent or sell your Personal Information in personally identifiable form to anyone. We may share your Personal Information with third parties as described in this section: 

  * **Information that’s no longer personally identifiable** : We may anonymize your Personal Information so that you are not individually identified, and provide that information to our partners. We may also provide aggregate usage information to our partners, who may use such information to understand how often and in what ways people use our Services, so that they, too, can provide you with an optimal online experience. However, we never disclose aggregate usage information to a partner in a manner that would identify you personally, as an individual. 
  * **Agents** : We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you; for example, we may use third party hosting providers or software developers to help implement and maintain the Services. Unless we tell you differently, our agents do not have any right to use the Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. 
  * **Business Transfers** : If we are involved in a reorganization, merger, acquisition or sale of our assets, your information may be transferred as part of that deal. We will notify you (for example, via a message to the email address associated with your account) of any such deal and outline your choices in that event. Other than as may be ordered by a bankruptcy or other court, the use and disclosure of all transferred Personal Information will be subject to this Privacy Policy, or to a new privacy policy if you are given notice of that new privacy policy and are given an opportunity to affirmatively opt-out. Personal Information submitted or collected after a transfer, however, may be subject to a new privacy policy adopted by the successor organization. 
  * **Related Companies** : We may share your Information with any of our parent companies, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control with us. 
  * **Protection of Amitree and Others** : We reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information that we believe is necessary to comply with law or court order; enforce or apply our applicable terms of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Amitree, our employees, our users, or others. 
  * **With your Permission** : For example, we may share your Information with insurance carriers offering the third-party insurance products made available to you through the Services. 

###  Is Personal Information about me secure? 

We will use very diligent efforts to protect the privacy of your account and other Personal Information we hold in our records, but unfortunately, we cannot guarantee complete security. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time. We use third party service providers such as Heroku and Amazon to host our services. You can read more about their security practices on their websites. 

###  Collection and Use of Information by Third Parties 

Amitree contractually prohibits its contractors, affiliates, vendors and suppliers from disclosing Personal Information received from us, other than under this Privacy Policy. 

Amitree provides links to other websites and other ways to communicate with third parties. When you communicate with third parties, the third party may also collect Personal Information. Many likely do. We do not control or have access to that Personal Information, and the collection and use of your personal information by those other websites and other means of communication will be governed by the third party privacy policy applicable to that site. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information provided to or gathered by third parties. The privacy policies of other websites should identify the entity collecting your personal information, and how it is being used. Amitree is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non-Amitree Websites, even if we link to them. Review the privacy policy of those sites before using them. 

###  Updating Your Personal Information and Privacy Preferences - What Personal Information can I access? 

You may update correct your personal information and privacy preferences through your account pages, where you can update basic account settings, such as your name, email, password, certain preferences. 

You can delete your account, which will remove most of your personal information. However, if you are working with others who have an account with us, some personal information about you will remain in their account. 

If you have questions, you can contact us at  [privacy@amitree.com](mailto:privacy@amitree.%63om), and you can also write to us at Amitree, Inc., 584 Castro Street #851, San Francisco, CA 94114, Attention: Privacy Officer. 

###  What if I have Questions or Concerns about this Policy 

If you have questions or concerns about our privacy policy, contact us at [privacy@amitree.com](mailto:privacy@amitree.%63om), or write to us. 

###  California Code Notice. 

Under California Civil Code Sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice identifying the categories of Personal Information which we share with our affiliates and/or third parties for marketing purposes, and providing contact information for such affiliates and/or third parties. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to [privacy@amitree.com](mailto:privacy@amitree.%63om)
